from PUSHSQUARE published March
20 2026 Years after announcement
Netflix's Assassin's Creed TV
series finally begins production
Login sign up Ki login or sign
up Years after announcement
Netflix's Assassin's Creed TV
series finally begins production
Years after announcement
Netflix's Assassin's Creed TV
series finally begins production
Netflix has announced that
production has begun at last on
its Assassin's Creed TV
adaptation Initially announced
back in October 2020 it's been
about five and a half years
without much of an update but
now we have a slightly better
idea of where we are in the
show's existence The post also
highlights many members of the
cast including Toby Wallace Lola
Petticrew Laura Marcus Tanzen
Crawford Zachary Hart Claes Bang
Nobun Rizwan and more The TV
show tells an original story and
is set to take place in Rome
circa 64 AD Here's the official
synopsis Assassin's Creed is a
high octane thriller centered on
the secret war between two
shadowy factions one set on
determining mankind's future
through control and manipulation
while the other fights to
preserve free will The series
follows its characters across
pivotal historical events as
they battle to shape humanity's
destiny There's no knowing
exactly when the show will be
ready to watch but given that
production is only just starting
now it's still going to be a
while to wait At least things
are moving at long last External
link